[
  {
    "Id": "KUTY8K3",
    "Question": "Who Created C?",
    "Answers": [
      "Bjarne Stoustrup",
      "Denis Ritchie",
      "James Gosling",
      "Charles Moore",
      "Dahl",
      "Nygaard"
    ],
    "AnswerIndex": 1,
    "Hint": "Not alive",
    "Explanation": "C, computer programming language developed in the early 1970s by American computer scientist Dennis M. Ritchie at Bell Laboratories (formerly AT\u0026T Bell Laboratories). C was designed as a minimalist language to be used in writing operating systems for minicomputers, such as the DEC PDP 7, which had very limited memories compared with the mainframe computers of the period.",
    "Contributor": "Farsit",
    "Ratings": null
  },
  {
    "Id": "681945720",
    "Question": "Which level of language is C\u002B\u002B?",
    "Answers": [
      "Low-Level",
      "Medium-Level",
      "High-Level",
      "Assembly-Level",
      "Intermediate-Level",
      "Human-Friendly"
    ],
    "AnswerIndex": 4,
    "Hint": "Related to college somehow",
    "Explanation": "C\u002B\u002B is a high-level object-oriented programming language that can also write procedural and generic code. It is used heavily in video game development1. C\u002B\u002B is classified as a middle-level language because it combines high-level and low-level language features. C\u002B\u002B is not higher level than C, but it has a different programming paradigm. C\u002B\u002B is grouped with lower level languages like C when compared to newer languages like Java, C#, Ruby, etc.",
    "Contributor": "Lord Kelvin",
    "Ratings": [
      5
    ]
  },
  {
    "Id": "70462396",
    "Question": "x\u002By=9,x-y=5 x=? y=?",
    "Answers": [
      "(3,2)",
      "(1,2)",
      "(6,2)",
      "(7,2)"
    ],
    "AnswerIndex": 3,
    "Hint": "5-y-y=1",
    "Explanation": "x = 7 and y = 2. \nx = 9-y.\nx-y=5\n9-y-y=5\n-2y=5-9\ny=2\nx=7",
    "Contributor": "Lord Kelvin",
    "Ratings": null
  },
  {
    "Id": "66307920",
    "Question": "What is Big O notation?",
    "Answers": [
      "Time Complexity",
      "Algorithm Frequency",
      "Program Oriententation",
      "Object Name"
    ],
    "AnswerIndex": 0,
    "Hint": "Property of an algorithm. expressed as O(n).",
    "Explanation": "Big O notation is a mathematical notation that describes the limiting behavior of a function when the argument tends towards a particular value or infinity. Big O is a member of a family of notations invented by Paul Bachmann, Edmund Landau, and others, collectively called Bachmann\u2013Landau notation or asymptotic notation. The letter O was chosen by Bachmann to stand for Ordnung, meaning the order of approximation. Can also be applied to computer algorithms.",
    "Contributor": "Farsit",
    "Ratings": null
  },
  {
    "Id": "58267605",
    "Question": "Which is abiding the Pythagorean theorem?",
    "Answers": [
      "z squared - x squared is equal to y squared",
      "y squared - x squared is equal to z",
      "x squared - y squared is equal to z squared",
      "x squared \u002B y squared is equal to y squared"
    ],
    "AnswerIndex": 0,
    "Hint": "Property of an algorithm. expressed as O(n).",
    "Explanation": "x^2 \u002B y^2 = z^2\nx^2 = z^2 - y^2\nx^2 - z^2 = -y^2\nz^2 - x^2 = y^2",
    "Contributor": "Farsit",
    "Ratings": null
  },
  {
    "Id": "06873825",
    "Question": "\u0027That\u0027s one small step for man, one giant ____ for mankind\u0027 Which word should be in the blank?",
    "Answers": [
      "Jump",
      "Advancement",
      "Leap",
      "Dive"
    ],
    "AnswerIndex": 2,
    "Hint": "Frogs",
    "Explanation": "This was from Neil A. Armstrong\u0027s famous words when we first went to the moon. The entire thing was \u0022That\u2019s one small step for man, one giant leap for mankind.\u0022",
    "Contributor": "Farsit",
    "Ratings": null
  },
  {
    "Id": "064745748",
    "Question": "What does GLHF stand for?",
    "Answers": [
      "Good Life High Five",
      "Good Luck Have Fun",
      "Great Life is Happiness and Freedom"
    ],
    "AnswerIndex": 1,
    "Hint": "Said before matches",
    "Explanation": "Just an acronym.",
    "Contributor": "Farsit",
    "Ratings": null
  },
  {
    "Id": "97597974",
    "Question": "Which of the following produces the highest dose of radiation?",
    "Answers": [
      "Being an astronaut",
      "Staying at Chernobyl Exclusion Zone",
      "Chain-Smoking"
    ],
    "AnswerIndex": 1,
    "Hint": "will probably cause you lung cancer",
    "Explanation": "",
    "Contributor": "Farsit",
    "Ratings": null
  },
  {
    "Id": "17216836",
    "Question": "Which Game was made by From Software",
    "Answers": [
      "Super Mario",
      "King\u0027s Field",
      "Lords of the Fallen",
      "Mortal Shell"
    ],
    "AnswerIndex": 1,
    "Hint": "Related to farms",
    "Explanation": "",
    "Contributor": "Lord Kelvin",
    "Ratings": null
  },
  {
    "Id": "96732911",
    "Question": "Which of the following was Neil A. Armstrong\u0027s achievement?",
    "Answers": [
      "First to set foot on Mars",
      "First to set foot on the moon",
      "Commanding the Gemini 7 mission",
      "Obtaining Master\u0027s Degree at University of Toronto"
    ],
    "AnswerIndex": 1,
    "Hint": "A place where you can get Lunar Dust. The answer should be obvious.",
    "Explanation": "",
    "Contributor": "Lord Kelvin",
    "Ratings": null
  }
]